myinkedspace.com 2015-03-20

# Privacy Policy | Zocialized

Updated on March 26th, 2012.

This Privacy Policy describes the information collected by Zocialized, operated by MyInkedSpace LLC., (we, us or MyInkedSpace), how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us. 

### The information we collect

In General. We may collect personal information that can identify you such as your name and email address and other information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information through our website, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world. 

Information you provide. We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as your name and email address. We also request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information such as your hometown or your username. 

Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information. We use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities on our site. 

Information collected automatically. We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our website. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website address. 

Cookies and Use of Cookie Data. When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the time and date of your visits, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. 

Information collected by third-parties. We may allow third-parties, advertising companies and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. 

### How we use the information we collect

In General. We may use information that we collect about you to: 

  1. deliver the products and services that you have requested. 
  2. manage your account and provide you with customer support. 
  3. perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others. 
  4. communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, or other third parties. 
  5. develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites. 
  6. verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes. 
  7. enforce or exercise any rights in our terms and conditions. 
  8. manage our business. 
  9. provide our advertisements to you when you visit other sites. 
  10. perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. 

### With whom we share your information

When you buy Bling Bucks or subscribe to VIP you share your personal information with the payment provider and are subject to their terms and conditions and privacy policy. 

Aggregated and non-personal information. We may share non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. 

### Third-party websites

There are a number of places on our website where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement on our website, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting. 

### How you can access your information

If you have an online account with us, you have the ability to review and update your personal information online by logging into your account and clicking on Settings (or Profile). More information about how to contact us is provided below. If you have an online account with us, you also may delete or disable your account at any time by visiting the "Help" page. If you delete or disable your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, enforce our terms and conditions, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our website or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies. 

### Your choices about collection and use of your information

You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our website. 

### How we protect your personal information

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. We want you to feel confident using our website to transact business. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure email. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission's website for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft. 

### Children's privacy

Although our website is a general audience site, we restrict the use of our service to individuals age 18 and above. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 

### How Does Zocialized Protect Children's Privacy?

The safety and privacy of children is extremely important to us.

Zocialized is a general audience web site that complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Our registration process is designed to restrict children under the age of 13 from becoming members of Zocialized and using our site. If we receive information suggesting that a user who has registered with Zocialized is under the age of 18, we require the user to provide evidence confirming that the user is at least 18 years old. If the user fails to provide such information within 48 hours, we immediately terminate the user's account and nullify all personally identifiable information displaying on the site. 

### Visiting our websites from outside the United States

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy. 

### No Rights of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our website from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies. 

### How to contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us by email: help@myinkedspace.com. 

### Linked information

Cookies: A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Cookies on our website do not link to or store your personal information. 

For example, when you sign in to our website, we will record your user or member ID and the name associated with your user or member ID in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. For security purposes, we will encrypt any usernames, passwords, and other user or member account-related data that we store in such cookies. In the case of sites and services that do not use a user or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies from our website to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our site, content and advertising. 

We may allow third-parties, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver (such as click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, etc.), and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party's privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies and provides information about this behavioral advertising practice (www.networkadvertising.org). This policy covers the use of cookies by Zocialized only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
